airplayit.com 2015-06-07

# Digiarty Software, Inc - Privacy Policy

##### Digiarty Software Customer Privacy Policy

We guaranty any of your information collected from our website will be handled very carefully as written below.

Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.

Your privacy is a priority at Digiarty Software, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

##### Why we collect personal information?

Your information will help us to deliver a superior customer service.

It enables us to give you convenient access to our products.

Your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

We collect your personal information, including your first name, last name, phone number, email address and other information that can be reasonable used to identify you.

##### How we may use it?

Product Registration, Online Support and Product Warranty

Answer to inquiries

To ship products or giveaways

E-mail Newsletters (product or services information, promotion, etc)

To make aggregate demographic data for R&D

Other purposes upon prior notice and approval

#####  When we disclose your information?

We will only share aggregate demographic information with our partners, investors and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Basically, personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties except in those cases:

When disclosure is required by court order.

When disclosure is required for account inquiry by Credit card companies (to avoid Credit Card Fraud).

Other purposes upon prior notice and approval.

##### Kids

If a child under 13 submits personal information to Digiarty Software and we learn that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.

It prevents for instance repetition of a same action during a short period.

Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.

Access Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. The Access Log Files information are not disclosed to third parties

##### Our companywide commitment to your privacy

This policy covers the Intel Corporate website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Digiarty employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

##### Questions:

Please send any questions or comments on our privacy practices to [contact@airplayit.com](mailto:contact@airplayit.com)
